Charlenne Alexander

charlennep@gmail.com (310) 770-8434



Professional Summary

I'm highly effective at anticipating and accommodating customer needs. Friendly, punctual and enthusiastic team player. I love to create ideas to help the place where I work to grown. Worked as a international model for almost 9 years. Every two to three months I was in a different city, country. Lived with people for all over the world and with that I learned how to adapt very fast. I am a very fast learner.

.....

Work History

03/2019 to present <u>Maggianos</u> (Nashville, TN)
Maitre D

04/2019 to present **Bob's Steak and Chop House @ Omni Hotel** (Nashville, TN)

Hostess

08/2018 to 02/2019 <u>CRUSTACEAN</u> (Beverly Hills, CA) VIP Reservation

.....

Education

2007 **COLEGIO CLARETIANO** (Brazil)

High School

2010 **PUC (Prontifica Universidade Catolica de Goias)** (Brazil)

University -Ceremonial and Events

2020 Vanderbilt

Full stack Web Developer